ALEX BOYE: Hey.
My name is Alex Boye.
One of the biggest things--one of the biggest ways you can gain stage presence, I'm going to tell you right now, okay, there's nothing else you need to know.
If you want someone to say that guy or that girl has amazing stage presence, all you have to do is have confidence.
I'm telling you, confidence hides a multitude of sins.
If you sing off key and you're confident, everyone thinks you're U2 from Bono.
If you--seriously, if you can't dance good and you do it with confidence, then they think you're that guy from Aerosmith.
Am I right or am I wrong?
Can he dance?
No!
But let me tell you how many people try to impersonate him?
Are you kidding me?!?
He has made millions of dollars.
You know why?
Because he does not care.
He does not care.
It is his own interpretation of his own emotion.
That's why now, many people are looking--"Oh, man, you're bad brother!" "Oh, go ahead. Oh. Oh." And he's got.... And you know Michael Jackson, he looks at--what's his name?
MAN: Steven Tyler?
ALEX BOYE: Steven Tyler.
MAN: Yeah.
ALEX BOYE: He looks at him, Michael Jackson, "Oh, you're bad, brother.
You're bad. I love you. Can I do a duet with you?" Why? It's not because he can dance, it is because he has so much confidence that he doesn't care and it makes it look like he's absolutely amazing as a dancer on stage.
So many people copy that.
We're going to talk about a little bit more about that on the other side later.